hustlermoneyblog.com 2011-12-19

# Privacy

**HustlerMoneyBlog** is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit  
our Web site. You can access **HustlerMoneyBlog** and browse our site without  
disclosing any of your personal data. **HustlerMoneyBlog** does not collect  
personal information about individuals, such as names and mailing or  
e-mail addresses, unless it is knowingly provided by the individual and  
he or she has agreed to the terms under which **HustlerMoneyBlog** will use  
it.

Disclosure of Information

**HustlerMoneyBlog** will not sell, trade, or rent your personal information  
to others. We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link  
information automatically logged by other means with personal data about  
specific individuals. We may use IP addresses to compile and provide  
aggregate statistics about our visitors, traffic patterns, and  
administer the site. This statistical information may also be related to  
third parties, but these statistics will not include any personally  
identifying information, track user’s movement, and gather broad  
demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked  
to personally identifiable information. We collect only the personal  
data that you may volunteer while using our services. We do not collect  
information about our visitors from other sources, such as public  
records or bodies, or private organizations.

If you do not want to have your information used in this way, send an  
e-mail message containing your name and email address to  **HustlerMoneyBlog** **[at] gmail.com**. We may release account information when such release is reasonably necessary to comply with the law; enforce the  
terms of any of our user agreements; or protect the rights, property,  
and safety of **HustlerMoneyBlog** , the users of its site, or others.

Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is important to us. For that  
reason, we do not collect or maintain information at our sites from  
those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our site is  
structured to attract anyone under 18.

External Web Sites

Please note that **HustlerMoneyBlog** contains links to other web sites.  
Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of  
these other sites. We encourage our users to be aware that when they  
leave our site that you read the privacy statements of each web site  
that might collect personally identifying information.

This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by **HustlerMoneyBlog**. If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy  
policy, please contact:  **HustlerMoneyBlog** **[at] gmail.com**

**Related posts:**

  1. [Disclaimer Policy](http://www.hustlermoneyblog.com/disclaimer-policy/ "Disclaimer Policy")
  2. [Finweb.com gives you good financial information](http://www.hustlermoneyblog.com/finwebcom-gives-you-good-financial-information/ "Finweb.com gives you good financial information")
